<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days</string>
    <string name="activity_one">Make a Vision Board Together</string>
    <string name="description_one">Looking toward the future is scientifically proven to make you happier. A collaborative vision board ensures that your goals are aligned and that you both feel excited about where you\'re going.</string>
    <string name="activity_two">Cuddle Session</string>
    <string name="description_two">Humans have an innate need for physical touch. Research shows that hugging and non-sexual cuddling between romantic couples lowered blood pressure and cortisol while boosting oxytocin.</string>
    <string name="activity_three">Describe Your Needs</string>
    <string name="description_three">Trust and open communication go hand-in-hand. A lack of communication about what you want is a key reason couples fight.</string>
    <string name="activity_four">Do a Puzzle Together</string>
    <string name="description_four">Couples should always have a feeling of cooperation. Setting aside time together toward a joint goal (however small) helps foster this.</string>
    <string name="activity_five">Make a Scrapbook</string>
    <string name="description_five">It\'s easier nowadays to look back at memories and stuff through our mobile phones or social media. But, why not try your hand at making a couple\'s scrapbook instead?</string>
    <string name="activity_six">Cook Dinner Together</string>
    <string name="description_six">Do you or your partner love cooking? Making dinner together can help you appreciate all the culinary work they do!</string>
    <string name="activity_seven">Make Your Monogram</string>
    <string name="description_seven">Design a creative monogram using a combination of your initials and then place this design on something special.</string>
    <string name="activity_eight">Do a Spaghetti Kiss</string>
    <string name="description_eight">If you’ve watched the movie Lady and the Tramp, you’ll surely remember its iconic scene: the spaghetti kiss!</string>
    <string name="activity_nine">Play Mini Golf</string>
    <string name="description_nine">From putting balls into clowns mouths to miniature windmills, a round of mini golf is a fun low stress environment in which to have a perfect day with your partner.</string>
    <string name="activity_ten">Kiss on top of a Ferris Wheel</string>
    <string name="description_ten">Some of the most romantic movies feature a smooch on the tippy-top of a ferris wheel.</string>
    <string name="activity_eleven">Sleep under the Stars</string>
    <string name="description_eleven">Camping out and sleeping outdoors with your significant other either in the mountains or your own backyard, is a great bonding experience.</string>
    <string name="activity_twelve">Watch the Sunset and Sunrise in One Day</string>
    <string name="description_twelve">Watching a beautiful sunrise or sunset cuddled up with your partner is the epitome of romance.</string>
    <string name="activity_thirteen">Climb to the top of a Mountain</string>
    <string name="description_thirteen">They say that “couples that climb together, stay together.”</string>
    <string name="activity_fourteen">Take a Spontaneous Relationship</string>
    <string name="description_fourteen">Got some time to spare with a desire to spice up things with your relationship a little bit?</string>
    <string name="activity_fifteen">Take a Hot Air Balloon Ride</string>
    <string name="description_fifteen">Jumping into a hot air balloon will take you on a thrilling and romantic ride in the sky.</string>
    <string name="activity_sixteen">Make Out at the Movies</string>
    <string name="description_sixteen">While this may not be every couple’s cup of tea, the thrill and riskiness of making out at the movies will be quite the experience.</string>
    <string name="activity_seventeen">Go to the Beach</string>
    <string name="description_seventeen">While this may not be every couple’s cup of tea, the thrill and riskiness of making out at the movies will be quite the experience.</string>
    <string name="activity_eighteen">Dine out at a Fancy Restaurant</string>
    <string name="description_eighteen">Sometimes it will be ages since your girlfriend and you went out to have a decent dinner without looking at your clocks.</string>
    <string name="activity_nineteen">Cliff Jumping while Holding Hands</string>
    <string name="description_nineteen">Grab your partners hand, plug your nose and take a leap of faith…together.</string>
    <string name="activity_twenty">Learn to Tango</string>
    <string name="description_twenty">The history of the Argentine tango originated in South America in the 1890s and has been called the sexiest dance in the world.</string>
    <string name="activity_twenty_one">Kiss Your Partner in the Rain</string>
    <string name='description_twenty_one'>As a relationship progresses we can forget the importance of just kissing!</string>
    <string name="activity_twenty_two">Do a Couple\'s Photo Session</string>
    <string name="description_twenty_two">Even if one of you is a little bit apprehensive about getting their photo taken at first, a professional photo shoot is a brilliant way to get some wonderful memories of your relationship.</string>
    <string name="activity_twenty_three">Picks Apple (or Berries) at a Farm</string>
    <string name='description_twenty_three'>Picking berries (especially during spring to summer) is another great outdoor activity that you can do with your partner.</string>
    <string name="activity_twenty_four">Hike a New Trail</string>
    <string name="description_twenty_four">If the two of you are interested in the outdoors, being active, or exploring something new, or the combination of all three, perhaps it’s time to take your romantic day on a hike?</string>
    <string name="activity_twenty_five">Jump Out of a Plane (Skydive!)</string>
    <string name="description_twenty_five">Since we are on a lifelong journey of making lasting memories with our partner, why not add something that goes above and beyond your comfort zone, like tandem skydiving?</string>
    <string name="activity_twenty_six">Kiss Under the Mistletoe During The Holidays</string>
    <string name="description_twenty_six">The holiday season can also be the time for romance.</string>
    <string name="activity_twenty_seven">Stay in a Cabin in the Woods</string>
    <string name="description_twenty_seven">Whether you\’re both the adventurous type or simply looking for a cozy and quiet getaway, staying at a cabin surrounded by nature is the perfect place to be.</string>
    <string name="activity_twenty_eight">Go Ice Skating</string>
    <string name="description_twenty_eight">When the winter months roll around and you simply can\'t spend another day inside, spend a day at your local ice rink.</string>
    <string name='activity_twenty_nine'>Do a Food Truck Tour</string>
    <string name="description_twenty_nine">Support local entrepreneurs while you enjoy a range of tasty treats.</string>
    <string name="activity_thirty">Visit Your Partner\'s Hometown</string>
    <string name="description_thirty">Heading to your partner\'s hometown is a great way to learn more about their childhood.</string>
</resources>